Link (in Vietnamese): http://vn.spoj.com/problems/NKJUMP/

Hopping is a traditional game of the Vietnamese people. People from the planet X also love this game a lot, so they made
their own version of the game. 

On a plane there are n circles, numbered from 1 to n. There is an integer ai inside the i-th circle. Two circles don't
have to have different numbers inside. Then people draw some arrow connecting some circles together. The rule of
connecting circles is that if there exist 3 numbers ai, aj, ak satisfying the condition ak = ai + aj, then there will be
two arrows from the i-th and j-th circle to the k-th circle. Players can only move along the arrows. The winner is the one
who finds the path going through the highest number of circles. Your task is to find that number.

Input

The first line contains an integer n (3 ≤ n ≤ 1000);
The second line contains n integers a1, a2, ..., an (ai ≤ 10 ^ 9, i=1, 2,..., n). Two consecutive numbers are separated
by a space.

Output

Print the highest number of circles.

Restriction

60% number of tests which value 60% of the final score has 3 ≤ n ≤ 100.

